Finding Aid for Jens Jensen Drawings and Papers 1903-1951
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Drawings
  - R
    - Rosenwald, Julius, Chicago, Illinois (Nimmons & Fellows; Lawrence Buck, architect)
      - A topographical survey for a portion of the estate of Mr. Julius Rosenwald, 1924; ROK16a; Yellow, black ink on linen and blueprint; topo. lines, elevations; at lower left, ""Book #18, Pages 30-34""; unsigned; 63 x 65 cm; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 79)
      - Detail plan of pool. Mrs. Rosenwald Memorial, 1929; ROK17; Red, black ink on back of graph linen paper; plan, cross-sections, details; signed; 77 x 47 cm; Scales vary (Map-case 58, Folder 79)
      - Sketch for Mrs. Rosenwald's Memorial, 1929; ROK18; Ink, green, red pencil on tracing paper; plan of pool, footpath, rockwork; unsigned; 43 x 44 cm; Scale: 1"" = 5' (Map-case 58, Folder 79)
        (neg. # JEN-Rok-18)
      - Entrance gate for estate of Mr. Julius Rosenwald, ROK19; Blueprint; plan, elevations; designed by Arthur Heun?; unsigned; 102 x 52 cm.; Scale: 1/2"" = 1' (Map-case 58, Folder 79)
      - Detail plan for pier, ROK20; Ink on linen; plan, elevation; notes; ""R.C. Fletcher, Contractor""; identified on verso as belonging to estate of J. Rosenwald; unsigned; 110 x 39 cm.; Scale: 1/4"" = 1' (Map-case 58, Folder 79)
    - Rosenwald, Morris, Chicago, Illinois (Howard Van Doren Shaw, architect)
      - Estate of Morris Rosenwald...Topo. plan., 1912; ROM1; Ink on linen; elevations, location, type of plantings, buildings, garden; residence at 4924 Woodlawn Ave.; signed; 96 x 51 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 79)
      - Grounds of Morris Rosenwald, Esq....Planting plan., 1913; ROM2; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; footpaths, seats; residence by Howard V. Shaw; notes; signed; 84 x 43 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 79)
        (neg. # JEN-Rom-2)
    - Ross, John D., Oak Park, Illinois
      - Grounds of Mr. John D. Ross. Plan of tape survey., 1913; ROS1; Ink on linen; location of buildings, slopes, trees, shrubs and proposed (?) building; signed; 62 x 68 cm. (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
    - Rubens, Harry, Glencoe, Illinois (George W. Maher, architect)
      - Planting plan for part of country home. Harry Rubens, Esq., 1903; RUB1; Two sheets; 1=ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; residence by G.W. Maher; signed; 1a=ink on linen; key to planting plan; signed; dated; 1=74 x 52 cm.; 1a=22 x 21 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Planting plan for part of country home. Harry Rubens, Esq., 1903; RUB2; Two sheets, ink on linen; 2=location, type, amounts of plantings; residence by G.W. Maher; signed; 2a=""key to planting plan""; signed; 2=75 x 52 cm.; 2a=28 x 31 cm. (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Planting plan showing planting adjacent to lodge and stables. H. Rubens, Esq., 1903; RUB3; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; stables by G.W. Maher; list of planting types; signed; 73 x 62 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Plan for conservatory. H. Rubens, Esq., 1903; RUB4; Ink on linen; plan, sections; signed; 72 x 55 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
        (neg. # JEN-Rub-4)
      - Plan of gardens and bluff. H. Rubens, Esq., 1904; RUB5; Ink on linen; location, types of plantings; residence by G.W. Maher; list of planting types; signed; 87 x 72 cm. (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Plan of vegetable garden. H. Rubens, Esq., 1904; RUB6; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed; 59 x 35 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Planting plan for the vegetable garden. H. Rubens, Esq., 1904; RUB7; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; notes; list of planting types; signed; 57 x 24 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Grading plan for the garden., 1904; RUB8; Red, green, brown ink on tracing paper; contour lines, cross-sections, elevations; signed (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Water system for the vegetable garden. Harry Rubens, Esq., 1904; RUB9; Ink on linen; signed; 43 x 27 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Water-drainage system for the garden and grounds adjacent to the residence. H. Rubens, Esq., 1904; RUB10; Pencil, red, green, brown ink on paper, location, size of pipes; pool; planting types added in pencil; signed; 77 x 71 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Planting plan for the garden of H. Rubens, Esq., 1904; RUB11; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; lists of planting types, objects; signed (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
        (neg. # JEN-Rub-11)
      - Additional planting plan for the garden of H. Rubens, Esq., 1906; RUB12; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; footpaths, pool, seats; flowers and times of year of blooming; signed; 39 x 35 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Planting plan for the garden of H. Rubens, Esq, RUB13; Red, black ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed; 82 x 40 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Preliminary planting plan. Country home of H. Rubens, Esq, RUB14; Ink on linen; location, type of some plantings for part of estate; building depicted designed by G.W. Maher; signed (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Sewer, drainage and water system for part of country home of Harry Rubens, Esq, RUB15; Ink on linen; plan, section; signed; 75 x 54 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Topographical chart of finished grounds west of residence site with proposed elevations for residence and slope towards bluff. H. Rubens, Esq, RUB16; Ink on linen; signed; 55 x 75 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
    - Rubovits, Toby, Chicago, Illinois
      - Estate of Mr. Toby Rubovits...Plan of grounds., 1913; RUD1; Ink on linen; residence by Arthur Heun; signed; 74 x 24 cm. (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Grounds of Mr. Toby Rubovits...Planting plan., 1913; RUD2; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; garden; revisions in pencil; residence by Arthur Heun; signed; 70 x 23 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
    - Rueckheim, L., Lakeside, Michigan
      - Drain and water system plan. Grounds of Mr. L. Rueckheim., 1919; RUF1; Red, green, black ink on linen; note, ""See Anderson, Lake Forest, for topo. survey""; signed; 78 x 42 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
        (neg. # JEN-Ruf-1)
    - Rumsey, Henry A., Lake Forest, Illinois
      - Estate of H.A. Rumsey...Topographical survey., 1912; RUM1; Ink on linen; contour lines, elevation; signed; 120 x 54 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
        (neg. # JEN-Rum-1)
      - Estate of Henry A. Rumsey...Garden plan., 1912; RUM2; Ink on tracing paper; garage by Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge; signed; 35 x 49 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
        (neg. # JEN-Rum-2)
      - Estate of Mr. Henry A. Rumsey...Planting plan., 1913; RUM3; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; gardens, notes; residence by Shepley, Rutan and Coolidge; unsigned; 108 x 54 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
        (neg. # JEN-Rum-3)
    - Ryerson, E.L., Lake Forest, Illinois
      - Estate of E.L. Ryerson, Esq....Drain plan., 1913; RYE1; Ink on tracing paper; residence by Howard Shaw; note, ""see drawing of April 1913""; notes, revisions in pencil; signed (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
        (neg. # JEN-Rye-1)
      - Estate of E.L. Ryerson...Planting plan for road border., 1913; RYE2; Pencil, ink on tracing paper; signed; 107 x 71 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Estate of E.L. Ryerson, Esq....Topographical plan., 1913; RYE3; Ink, pencil on tracing paper; elevations; residence by Howard Shaw; signed; 77 x 70 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 60' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Estate of E.L. Ryerson, Esq....Planting plan for garden., 1914; RYE4; Ink on linen; type of plantings; gardens, pool; note, ""Suggested by Mr. E.L. Ryerson""; signed; 122 x 81 cm. (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
        (neg. # JEN-Rye-4)
      - Estate of E.L. Ryerson, Esq....Water and drain plan., 1914; RYE5; Ink on linen; residence by Howard Shaw; signed; 80 x 65 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 60' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Estate of E.L. Ryerson, Esq....Plan for roadside planting., 1914; RYE6; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type, amounts of plantings; unsigned; 38 x 60 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 60' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - Estate of E.L. Ryerson, Esquire...Plan for electric lights along drives., 1916; RYE7; Ink on linen; unsigned; 68 x 64 cm. (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - A plan of survey for the garden. Estate of Mr. E.L. Ryerson., 1920; RYE8; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type of some plantings; gardens, pools, tea house; unsigned; 110 x 69 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
        (neg. # JEN-Rye-8)
      - A plan of survey for the house. Terrace and lawn areas. Estate of Mr. E.L. Ryerson., 1920; RYE9; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type of some plantings; residence by Howard Shaw; unsigned; 89 x 63 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
      - A plan of survey for the mall. Estate of Mr. E.L. Ryerson., 1920; RYE10; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type of trees, court; unsigned; 72 x 48 cm. (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
        (neg. # JEN-Rye-10)
      - Grade survey. Ryerson Place, RYE11; Pencil, blue, red, green ink on tracing paper; elevations; residence by Howard Shaw; unsigned; 80 x 65 cm.; No scale (Map-case 58, Folder 80)
  - S
    - Saint Elizabeth's Church, Glencoe, Illinois
      - Preliminary sketch. Church of Saint Elizabeth., 1914; SAI1; Colored pencil on tracing paper; signed; 90 x 51 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 16' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
      - General plan. Church of St. Elizabeth., 1914; SAI2; Ink on linen; location of buildings, gardens, plantings; signed; 94 x 51 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 16' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
    - Sanford, Hugh W., Knoxville, Tennessee (Spencer & Powers, architect)
      - House and garage for Hugh W. Sanford., 1917; SAN1; Blueprint; ""general plan of buildings and grounds"", with topo. lines; Spencer and Powers, architects; signed; 101 x 73 cm.; Scale: 1/16"" = 1' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
      - H.W. Sanford., 1929; SAN2; Pencil, red ink on tracing paper; topo. lines gardens, pools, footpaths, plantings; unsigned; 130 x 49 cm.; No scale (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
    - Scarbrough, H.C., Highland Park, Illinois
      - Topographical survey. Estate of H.C. Scarbrough, Esq., 1909; SCB1; Red, black ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations; location, types of trees; signed; 57 x 41 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
    - Schlesinger, F., Milwaukee, Wisconsin
      - Detail of concrete wall for the estate of F. Schlesinger, Esq., 1917; SCE1; Pencil on tracing paper; plan, section, elevation; notes; unsigned; 64 x 61 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
      - Plan for fascine work for the estate of F. Schlesinger, Esq, SCE2; Pencil on tracing paper; top of sheet torn away; plan, section, detail; unsigned; 87 x approx. 150 cm.; Scales vary [none given for plan] (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
      - Topographical survey of E 1/2 of lot 6 and lots 7,8,9, and 10 in Lake Park Addition. 18th Ward, SCE3; Ink on linen; note at bottom, ""F. Schlesinger, Milwaukee""; contour lines, elevations; notes; unsigned; 91 x 65 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
    - Scott, F.H., Hubard Woods, Illinois
      - Grounds of F.H. Scott, Esq....Planting plan., 1914; SCH1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; gardens, pool; amounts of plantings in pencil; signed; 85 x 27 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
      - F.H. Scott, SCH2; Red, black ink on linen; contour lines, elevations; location of buildings, trees; unsigned; 85 x 27 cm. (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
      - Sketch plot plan of grounds. Mr. F.H. Scott's residence, SCH3; Pencil on tracing paper; some contour lines; location of buildings, water, sewage tiles; elevations; unsigned; 150 x 49 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 15' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
    - Scott, John W., Glencoe, Illinois
      - Estate of John W. Scott, Esq....Plan of topo. survey., 1914; SCJ1; Ink on linen; elevations, locations of trees; signed; 73 x 52 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
      - Plan for estate of J.W. Scott, Esq., 1914; SCJ2; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings; footpaths, seats; signed; 67 x 55 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
    - Scott, R.L., Evanston, Illinois
      - Planting plan for the residence of Mr. R.L. Scott, 1915; SCL1; Ink on linen; location, types of plantings; footpaths, trellises; notes; signed; 75 x 48 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
    - Seabury, C.W., Oak Park, Illinois (White & Christie, architect)
      - Estate of C.W. Seabury...Planting plan., 1912; SEB1; Red, black ink on linen; location, types, amounts of plantings; gardens, pool, seats, steps (?); residence by White and Christie; signed; 61 x 57 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
        (neg. # JEN-Seb-1)
    - Seaman, George G., Taylorville, Illinois
      - A sketch. Estate of Col. and Mrs. Geo. Seaman., 1920; SEG1; Pencil on tracing paper; location of buildings, trees, proposed plantings, footpaths, council rings, gardens; unsigned; 87 x 59 cm. (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
      - Untitled, SEG2; Ink, red, black pencil on linen; estate as depicted in SEG1, with location of proposed roads, orchard, pool, garden; unsigned; 89 x 60 cm.; [Scale: 1"" = 60'] (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
      - Planting plan for the estate of Col. Geo. Seaman., 1921; SEG3; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; lake, gardens, tennis court, orchard, council ring, footpaths; notes; three red arrows marking direction of photographs (#19, 20, 21); signed; 128 x 84 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 40' (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
      - Planting plan for garden areas. Estate of Col. Geo. G. Seaman., 1921; SEG4; Yellow, black ink on linen; location, type of plantings; gardens, tennis court, outbuildings (Map-case 58, Folder 81)
    - Shire, M.E., Highland Park, Illinois
      - Plat of survey..., 1922; SHI1; Blueprint; location of residence outlined in pencil (scale: 1"" = 30'); unsigned; 31 x 49 cm.; [Scale: 1"" = 30'] (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
    - Silberman, S., Chicago, Illinois
      - Detail plan of pool. Estate of S. Silberman. 4801 Ellis Ave., 1917; SIB1; Pencil on tracing paper; plan, cross-section, details; signed; 69 x 33 cm.; Scales vary (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Plan of flower garden. Mr. S. Silberman., 1917; SIB2; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type of plantings; pool, seats, footpaths; signed; 32 x 38 cm. (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
    - Simms, E.F., Paris, Kentucky
      - Plan of topo. survey for the estate of E.F. Simms, Esq., 1915; SIE1; Red, black ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations; signed; 95 x 158 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 60' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
        (neg. # JEN-Sie-1)
      - Estate of E.F. Simms, Esq....Plan of topo. survey for entrance drive, #2., 1915; SIE2; Pencil, red, black ink on linen; elevations, distances; unsigned; 83 x 54 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 60' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
        (neg. # JEN-Sie-2)
      - Estate of E.F. Simms, Esq....Main entrance drive. Station #0-#31., 1916; SIE3; Red, black ink on linen; plan of main entrance gate, cross-section of drive, plan of drive; signed; 89 x 94 cm. (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
        (neg. # JEN-Sie-3)
      - Estate of E.F. Simms, Esq....Main entrance drive. Station #31-#61, 1916; SIE4; Pencil, red, black ink on linen; elevations, distances; signed; 105 x 78 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 60' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
        (neg. # JEN-Sie-4)
      - Estate of E.F. Simms, Esq....Entrance drive No. 2., 1916; SIE5; Red, black ink on linen; plans of entrance gate, drive; elevations, distances; notes indicating location, direction of photo; signed; 84 x 60 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 60' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
        (neg. # JEN-Sie-5)
      - Estate of E.F. Simms, Esq. Plan for the swimming pool., 1916; SIE6; Red, black ink on linen; plan, sections of pool, detail of drain; signed; 99 x 54 cm. (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
        (neg. # JEN-Sie-6)
      - A planting plan for the gardens of E.F. Simms, Esq, SIE7; Red, black ink on linen; location, types of plantings; gardens, pools, footpaths; notes; signed; 128 x 104 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
        (neg. # JEN-Sie-7)
    - Simms, E.F., Spring Station, Kentucky
      - Plan for picking garden. Estate of W.E. Simms, Esq., 1911; SIM1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings, some amounts; signed; 64 x 77 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Planting plan. Formal garden. Estate of W.E. Simms., 1911; SIM2; Red, black ink on linen; location, types of plantings; trellises, vases, seats, steps, footpaths; notes; signed; 97 x 63 cm. (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Grade plan. Rock garden. Estate, W.E. Simms, Esq., 1912; SIM3; Red, black ink on linen; plan, sections, pool, arbors, seats, footpaths; signed; 100 x 85 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Planting plan. Estate of W.E. Simms, Esq., 1912; SIM4; ; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings for portions of estate; notes; signed; 101 x 96 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Road plan. Estate of W.E. Simms, Esq., 1912; SIM5; Pencil, red, black ink on linen; elevations, distances; signed; 102 x 90 cm. (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Planting plan for rock garden. Estate of W.E. Simms., 1912; SIM6; Ink on linen; location, type, amount of plantings; arbor, footpaths, pool; notes; signed; 98 x 87 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Grade plan for pool. Estate of W.E. Simms, Esq., 1913; SIM7; Ink on linen; plan, sections; signed; 76 x 35 cm.; Scales vary. (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Estate of W.E. Simms, Esq....Plan of topo. survey., 1914; SIM8; Red, black ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations; signed; 76 x 103 cm. (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Design of urn and flambeau. Mr. W.E. Simms., 1915; SIM9; Ink on linen; signed; 29 x 18 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 1' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Planting plan showing changes in the formal garden. Estate of W.E. Simms., 1915; SIM10; ; Pencil on tracing paper; location, types of plantings; seats, urns, steps, formal gardens; 94 x 64 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - A planting plan for the estate of W.E. Simms, Esq., 1916; SIM11; Two sheets; 11=ink on linen; location, type of plantings, gardens, pool, roads; notes; signed; 11a=green, blue, brown, black pencil on tracing paper overlay; traces present [c.1962?] location of buildings, plantings, roads; notes (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Planting plan for area around the swimming pool on the W.E. Simms Estate., 1916; SIM12; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; tennis court, pool, footpaths; two sections; signed; 121 x 80 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
        (neg. # JEN-Sim-12)
      - Plan for a rose garden. Estate of W.E. Simms, Esq., 1917; SIM13; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type of plantings; footpaths, steps; unsigned; 39 x 64 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Study for a rose and water panel garden. Estate of W.E. Simms., 1917; SIM14; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type of plantings; footpaths, water panel; section; signed; 39 x 64 cm. (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Plan for a rose garden for the estate of W.E. Simms, Esq., 1917; SIM15; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type of plantings; footpaths, steps, seats; unsigned; 39 x 64 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
      - Untitled, SIM16; Pencil, red, black ink on linen; at lower right, ""W.E. Simms"" printed in pencil; plan of estate, with residence, gardens, outbuildings, elevations; unsigned; 65 x 60 cm.; No scale (Map-case 59, Folder 82)
    - Simpson, J., Glencoe, Illinois
      - Revised plan. Estate of Mr. J. Simpson., 1913; SIP1; Ink on linen; location, type, amounts of plantings around pool; signed; 78 x 37 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
    - Skinner, J.F., Oak Park, Illinois
      - Plan for grounds of Mr. J.F. Skinner., 1911; SKI1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings, tennis court, pool, seats; cross-section of pool area; signed; 62 x 59 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
        (neg. # JEN-Ski-1)
    - Smith, C.F., Highland Park, Illinois
      - Drain plan for bluff. Grounds of Mr. C.F. Smith., 1912; SMC1; Red, black ink on tracing paper; signed; 46 x 36 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
      - Estate of C.F. Smith...Topographical survey on bluff., 1912; SMC2; Ink on linen; elevations; signed; 47 x 36 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
      - Planting plan for bluff. Grounds of C.F. Smith., 1912; SMC3; Red, black ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed; 44 x 34 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
    - Smith, Fred B., Terre Haute, Indiana (Spencer & Powers, architect)
      - Planting plan for property of Frank S. Smith., 1916; SMI1; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type, amounts of plantings; pool, footpath, seats; signed; 58 x 34 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
      - Design for garden house. F.B. Smith., 1909; SME1; Red, black ink on tracing paper; various views, plans; signed; approx. 90 x 54 cm.; No scale (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
      - Plans for the garden pillars and concrete bench. Mr. F.B. Smith., 1909; SME2; Red, black ink on linen; signed; 53 x 29 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 1' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
      - Planting plan. Design for country estate of Mr. Fred B. Smith., 1909; SME3; Two sheets; 3=ink on linen; location, type of plantings; signed; 3a=pencil on tracing paper overlay; outline of residence; number, location, direction of several photos; 3=111 x 80 cm.; 3a=52 x 72 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
      - Topographical survey for estate of Mr. Fred B. Smith, Esq., 1909; SME4; Ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations; location of buildings; pencil lines down middle with note, ""Print this [left] side only""; signed; 110 x 84 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 50' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
      - Grade and drain plan of road. Mr. F.B. Smith., 1910; SME5; Red, black ink on tracing paper; plans, cross-sections, profiles of road; signed; 96 x 38 cm. (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
      - Enlarged and revised plan for the gardens of Mr. F.B. Smith, Esq., 1910; SME6; Two sheets; 6=ink on linen; signed; 6a=pencil on tracing paper overlay; location of buildings; numbers, location, direction of photos; 6=104 x 54 cm.; 6a=100 x 52 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 20' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
      - Profile of drive showing n. and s. edges of drive for estate of F.B. Smith, SME7; Ink, pencil on graph paper; elevations, notes; unsigned; 80 x 26 cm.; No scale (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
    - Smith, Frederick H., Peoria, Illinois
      - Landscape design and planting plan for country estate of Frederick H. Smith, Esq., 1908; SMG1; Ink on linen; location, type of plantings; location of drives, pool; signed; 170 x 44 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
      - Drainage and topographical plans for country estate of Frederick H. Smith, Esq., 1908; SMG2; Ink on linen; topo. lines, elevations; signed; 172 x 42 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
    - Smith, Frank S., Oak Park, Illinois
      - Planting plan for property of Frank S. Smith., 1916; SMI1; Pencil on tracing paper; location, type, amounts of plantings; pool, footpath, seats; signed; 58 x 34 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 10' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
    - Smith, Thomas, St. Joseph, Michigan
      - Plat of Thos. Smith farm., 1914; SMM1; Blueprint; location of trees, buildings; at lower right, ""Will J. Cleary""; unsigned; 95 x 44 cm.; Scale: 1"" = 30' (Map-case 59, Folder 83)
    - Smithers, Perry L., Wilmette, Illinois